{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Wise",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/surname",
    "object": "Wise",
    "human_readable": "The surname of Robert Wise is Wise.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9845511317253113,
            "question": "What is the surname of Robert Wise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9454931616783142,
            "question": "Is 'Wise' Robert Wise's last name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.902914822101593,
            "question": "Who has the surname Wise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9012853503227234,
            "question": "What is the last name commonly associated with Robert Wise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8926378488540649,
            "question": "What is Robert Wise referred to by?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8521435856819153,
            "question": "What is the given name of someone whose surname is Wise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8337315917015076,
            "question": "What family name does Robert Wise share?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7816271185874939,
            "question": "If someone's surname is Wise, what is their last name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7518818378448486,
            "question": "If you were writing about Robert Wise, what name would you use for his family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.724013090133667,
            "question": "How would you identify Robert Wise based on his family name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The surname of Robert Wise is Wise.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5601_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were writing about Robert Wise, what name would you use for his family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5601_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If someone's surname is Wise, what is their last name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5601_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What family name does Robert Wise share?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5601_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5601_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5601_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5601_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5601_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5601_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5601_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5601_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5601_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5601_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5601_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents confirm that the surname of Robert Wise, the American film director and editor mentioned in one of the files, is indeed \"Wise\". This information can be found in several of the files, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5601/re-ranker-msmarco/31.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the surname \"Wise,\" confirming that Robert Wise has the surname Wise."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}